- I'm leaving.
- Leaving? Where you going?
- I'm going to Miami.
You've never thought
about anything else?
- I like Tasha.
You finally texting her?
- No.
- I'm pregnant.
- Well. what you thinking?
- No. no.
I mean. I get the offer.
I really do. but--
- I mean. and if this
is about space.
we just go with one
of the bigger units.
I ain't renovated
nothing up there yet.
but. I mean.
that's the easiest part.
- I found a doctor in Miami.
Highly recommended
and works with my medical.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
- OK.
So what. you want to have
the baby in Miami?
- I mean. I--
I just bought a place.
got a job.
- I know. but--
I mean. my family's here.
Help is here.
I'm here.
- And I'm used to
doing things by myself.
I'll be fine.
We'll figure it out.
- But you know
you not by yourself.
- I know. Kevin.
but we barely know each other.
- We've known each other
since the Academy.
- And then we didn't see
each other for a decade.
and then it was one night.
And I didn't hear from you.
which is fine.
Look. I don't want to argue.
- Mm-mm.
We're not arguing.
Well. I'm here now.
I ain't going nowhere.
- I know. Kevin.
and I appreciate that.
But I just--
I think Miami
makes the most sense.
- You sure Miami actually
or is that just
the easiest thing to do?
Does any of this feel easy?
Look. can we just
get the check.
talk about it later?
- Mm-hmm.
Excuse me.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
We should go.
I can't be here drunk. man.
She's gonna be fine.
- We can't just go.
- Hold up.
Hey. what y'all got going on?
- Uh. nothing.
Someone's hurt. and an
ambulance is supposed to come.
- Wait. somebody's hurt?
- Yo.
Dude. where's the ambulance?
- Hold on.
We're police.
Stay here.
Who's hurt?
- My--my girlfriend.
she got attacked.
I called 911. but they're not--
- Where is she?
- She's over here.
- OK.
Come on. let's go.
I'll hold it here
till the squads arrive.
- All right. all right.
Hold it down.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean. attacked?
- I found her upstairs.
She was blindfolded
and tied up.
- Is the person who
attacked her still here?
- I don't know.
- What the hell happened?
- I-I don't know.
I found her like this.
There were two men up here.
- OK. she got a pulse.
she got a pulse.
What'd the men look like?
- I--
I didn't see their faces.
They wore masks.
I came up here. and they
attacked me from behind.
slammed me against the wall.
and then they were gone. fast.
Is she alive?
- Yeah. she's alive.
she's alive.
- 911. what's your emergency?
- Yeah. 911. this is
Officer Kevin Atwater.
badge number 52784.
I'm off-duty on scene at--
what's this address?
- Uh--
- What's the address?
- 1523 Banks.
It's Emily's house.
on the second floor.
I'm gonna need an ambo
and some units.
You should already have a call
to this location.
Hey. come on.
we gotta get out of here.
Take my phone.
Talk to the operator.
Tell them what's going on
and what we're doing.
We gotta go.
- No. no. my--my girlfriend.
she--she got attacked.
- It's OK. It's OK.
We gotta go.
- Kevin!
- Yeah. I got no descriptor
of the offenders.
just male.
They might be in the crowd.
- OK.
I didn't let anyone leave.
- Police!
- Hey. police.
We're both police.
I'm Intelligence.
She's Miami PD.
You gotta clear it upstairs.
Do not let anybody leave.
It looks like
a robbery gone wrong.
We got a female assault victim.
trauma to the head.
no signs of sexual assault.
Her name is Emily. right?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
- OK. let's get her
out of here.
- Mom.
- Hey.
- Hey. hon.
Uh. we're gonna get you
some help. OK?
- I want my mom.
- OK. we're gonna get her.
Do you know who did this
to you?
- I want my mom.
- We got her. Stay back.
- OK. I'm gonna go with her.
- OK.
- OK. I'll call you. Go.
- All right.
- Mom.
- Did Emily's parents know what
was going on here tonight?
- No. it's spring break.
Emily's parents
are out of town.
so she threw a party.
- Were you with Emily
when she got attacked?
- No.
No. but I. uh--
I realized I hadn't seen her
in a while. so I went looking.
I walked by the bedroom.
It was really dark.
but I heard her screaming.
and I ran in.
and these two guys jumped me.
- And you're sure
it was two of them?
- Uh-huh.
- And you don't remember
what they looked like?
- I--I told you.
I don't know.
It was--they were dressed
all in black and wearing masks.
- Did they say anything to you?
Did they threaten you?
- No.
No. they took off right away.
like I said.
- OK.
And you don't think
anybody else got a good look?
- I don't know.
I don't--
- OK.
All right. Ellis.
we're gonna help you write down
everything you remember. OK?
You're doing good.
- Ellis. please come with me.
Security cams were turned off.
so we got no video.
It's hard to say
if that's because of the kids
or whoever these men are.
- Is it a robbery gone wrong?
- Yeah.
that's what it feels like.
Crew walks through
the front door.
They pretend
they want to party.
Come up here looking to score.
Emily walks in on them.
They attack her.
- It's excessive.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Robbery/Homicide
contacted me.
Apparently this ain't
the first hit.
They got two
previous burglaries
at house parties on
the Gold Coast this month.
but this is the first time
it got violent.
- Got a sneaker print?
- Yeah.
I got techs working that.
Tasha Fox said Emily
never regained consciousness.
We lost her in the ambo.
- All right. we'll take it.
Get the team here.
Talk to every kid downstairs.
- I don't have to
tell you anything.
I know my rights.
I want my phone call.
- You're not booked.
You don't need a phone call.
- My mom will sue you.
- OK.
We can arrest you
'cause you're drunk
and you're under 21. so--
- It's also a felony
to have a fake ID.
- Look. I don't know anything.
- How'd you know Emily?
- Who's Emily?
- Emily Johnson.
This is her house.
- Never met her.
I'm from Winnetka.
- OK. How'd you find out
about the party?
- Insta.
- Did you notice anyone
suspicious coming or going?
- No. man.
It was a good party
till you guys showed up.
- Well. I'm sorry
to wreck your fun.
- Crime scene is closed.
No one in or out.
- Take it up
with your supervisor.
- Do you live here?
- My kid is in there.
Move. please.
- Sir. Sir.
- Excuse me.
this is a closed crime scene.
- Alan Powell. attorney.
I'm obligated to remind you
that if any of these
individuals is under 18.
their parents should be
present for questioning.
And you do not have a right
to their phones
without consent or a warrant.
- Yes. sir.
We're absolutely
getting consent.
- I'm not seeing much of that.
- We're Ellis' parents.
I'm Toni Powell.
This is my husband.
- We received a call from
your superintendent's office.
He's a friend.
- Your son is safe.
I can take you right to him.
- Have you contacted
everyone's parents?
If not.
then that's a priority--
- Alan!
I want to see Ellis.
A child just died.
- Yes. yes. I know.
That's why I'm talking to
the officer. and he's gonna--
- Sir. ma'am.
Right this way.
- Thank you.
- He really tried to
represent all of them?
- Mm-hmm.
Wealthy-ass parents.
more worried about them
catching drinking charges
than helping a murder case.
- Well. luckily for us.
these kids make
everything public.
They already have
a name for it--
#EmilyHouseHeist.
That girl was begging
for her mama.
- Oh. God. Kev.
Techs on the scene ID'd
the bloody shoe impression.
It's a pair of specific Pumas.
limited run.
Check that out.
- Wait.
I think I saw
some shoes like this.
- Yeah?
Let's look.
- Right there.
Right there in the back.
- OK.
Yeah. look at that.
Check out that timestamp--
9:47 p.m.. and Ellis.
he called 911 at 10:13 p.m.
- So it fits.
This could be
one of our offenders.
- There's gotta be
more images of him.
Did Fox go home?
- Mm-mm.
She's at my crib.
- Yeah. that's what I meant.
Is she here long?
- Probably not.
Had a rough night.
a little bit.
- Well. it's 4:00 a.m.
Why don't you go back
to your place.
tag out for a few hours?
- No. I'm OK.
- Get out of here.
- I know what you're doing.
- Mm-hmm.
Morning.
- Good morning.
Sorry if I woke you.
I can't sleep.
Pregnancy is doing
weird things to me.
Making coffee.
- Thank you.
- Did you ID your offender?
- No. not yet.
The crew blended in with
the party. disappeared.
Those kids were very high.
very drunk. extremely helpful.
- Is that one of them?
Did you clock his ring?
- What's this.
some kind of class ring?
- Not just any class ring.
That's a high school
football division
championship ring
from my old high school.
Your suspect.
he's from Roseland.
He's a long way from home.
- Ring belongs
to a football player.
Grant High School. from
either year they won state--
2019 or 2022.
About 200 players
and staff each year.
- Geographically. it also fits
the other two burglaries.
We noticed a pattern.
These are the other two house
parties that the crew hit.
That's around Emily's house
right here.
everything in the Gold Coast.
and everything
one block away
from a Red Line stop.
As we know. the Red Line goes
all the way from the Gold Coast
down here to Roseland.
- Crew's using
the Wicked River.
- That's what we called it
in the 11th District too.
Hop on. hop off. rip.
smash. steal. head on home.
- Well. that's good.
We can use this.
Let's run all Ventra card
records from those stops.
- I can run the connection
to Grant High.
- These are the school records
with the coaches.
managers. and trainers.
- Yeah. Robbery/Homicide
sent us
their stolen item inventory
from the past two hits.
I can run that through
the Roseland pawnshops.
- Oh. well. most of them
won't be on the books.
They're not legit. so they
won't be on the databases.
- Do you have a lead on those?
- Hey.
you're not CPD anymore.
We can't ask you to work this.
- I'm offering.
I can sign a waiver.
- OK. no need.
You find anything. we log you
as a confidential source.
- Good with me.
- OK.
- That's the place.
Side alley. black gate.
The last one on our list.
- Good.
Hey. I know it's not
under the best circumstances.
but it is nice having you here.
I'm a big fan of Kev's.
- Yeah. yeah.
Yeah. he wants me
to move back to Chicago.
- Oh. really?
Of course. he would.
And who wouldn't want
to leave Miami for this?
Yeah. Miami's not all
it's cracked up to be.
Kind of hate it. actually.
- Really?
- Yeah. but it's fine.
We'll figure it out before
the baby pops out. hopefully.
- What?
- He didn't tell anyone.
- No. he didn't.
Um--but that's amazing.
This is great news.
- Yeah. it is.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. thank you.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Yo. you Frankie D?
- Maybe.
Who are you?
- I'm Carlo's half-sister.
You know Carlo.
from up on Maypole?
Carlo. with the bad arm.
bad attitude.
- G-Park?
- Yeah.
Well. he said you got
the good flat screens.
And my girl here.
she don't want to deal
with the Geek Squad.
you feel me?
- Look.
I don't want no trouble.
- Hook it up. then.
Or I could call him.
I really don't want to--
- All right. all right.
all right. all right.
Follow me.
- All right.
All right.
We got. uh--we got OLEDs.
LCDs. even QLEDs.
All mint in the box.
so you tell me
what you want to do.
- Mm. this stuff is nice.
What about that ring?
- Good eye.
Just came in recently.
Uh. one of a kind.
Not cheap. but maybe
we can work out something.
- OK.
It's funny. it looks like
a ring a friend of mine has.
- Mm-hmm.
- But that one was stolen
last night. so...
- I mean. clearly
it's not the same one.
- No. 'cause that one's
one of a kind.
- How's. uh.
Carlo doing these days?
He still locked up in Joliet?
- Dixon. actually.
- You sure?
- I'm sure. 'cause
I'm the one who put him there.
Where'd you get
the stolen merch. Frank?
- Kim. what'd you get?
- Frankie folded.
He was terrified
of being brought in.
He said the stolen property
from that robbery
was brought in by a local guy.
a guy named Dwayne Coleman.
We ran him.
He attended Grant in 2019.
24 years old. no priors.
- Yeah. I got him right here.
All right. Dwayne Coleman.
Yeah. he was the running back
for the team.
being eyed by Michigan State
until he blew out his knee.
second-to-last game
of the year.
- Run his socials.
- DMV has him listed
in Roseland.
- Yeah. Roseland makes sense.
- All right.
- OK. here we go.
That's the ring right there.
- And there he is
wearing Pumas.
This is one of our guys.
- Mm-hmm.
Wait. he literally
just posted a story.
Idiot.
We can grab him up right there.
Burgess. Dwayne Coleman
is going to Clark and Division.
We're gonna meet you
right there.
- Copy you.
- I'll call Voight.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
CPD.
Train's inbound.
60 seconds out.
- Perfect.
Posted at the exit above.
- Copy you.
I got eyes on Coleman.
Brown jacket. gray hoodie.
moving towards the east exit.
Headed to you.
- Copy that. We'll be ready.
- Fox. I'll take the stairs.
You get the escalator.
- Got you.
Excuse me.
- There's too many people.
I'm gonna lose him
at the east exit.
- We're right up top.
We'll catch him as soon
as he steps out.
I got eyes.
Coleman.
Dwayne Coleman.
Slow down for me.
Coleman.
Whoa.
Whoa. hold up. Hey!
- Hey.
I got you.
Call an ambo. Ocean.
He got stabbed.
- 5021 Ocean.
Roll an ambo to...
- Who did this?
Know who did it?
Huh?
- Move. move. move!
- Come on!
Just hold on.
- Excuse me. excuse me.
What happened?
- I don't know what happened.
Somebody was right here.
I--I missed it.
- Description?
- I didn't see the offender.
I don't have a description.
I missed the offender.
Get everybody back.
- Hey. hey.
Step back. step back.
Did anybody see anything?
No. no. no. stay.
- Everyone.
can you move back this way?
- OK. Move back.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Crime scene.
- Never got eyes
on the offender.
It was too crowded.
happened fast.
- You pull cams?
- Yeah. it was definitely
a male offender.
It was over in seconds.
- All right.
this is the moment of attack.
That's Coleman.
That's the offender.
He practically guts him.
Nobody even slows down.
- Weapon recovered?
- Still searching. but he
likely carried it out with him.
- You don't get a view
of the offender's face.
but he appears
about 6 foot tall.
slender build. about a buck 75.
- Whoever the offender was.
knew Coleman
and knew Coleman
was gonna be right here.
It was probably whoever
he was supposed to meet.
Just took him by surprise.
- Sarge. Kev. Coleman's phone.
Last call he made
was an hour ago.
to an Ellis Powell.
- Ellis Powell.
Emily's boyfriend?
The kid that we met
at the scene?
- Same guy who called 911.
- Coleman called him right
before he got on the train.
- 6 foot. thin.
it fits.
- We appreciate this.
Mr. Powell.
Your son was helpful.
Hoping he can give us
a bit more background.
- If it'll help.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. yeah.
there were a lot of people
from other colleges there.
- Always how
these things go. right?
Uh. there's actually a person
who we think was at the party.
We just want to know
if you know him.
- I mean. yeah.
We. uh--
we used to play football
against each other.
- Mm.
So you know his name?
- We called him Coleman.
His last name.
- Right.
That's really helpful.
Do you think you saw him
at the party?
Was he there?
- Uh. it was so crowded. I--
- Are you still in touch
with Coleman?
- Uh.
I don't play football anymore.
- So that's a no?
- I mean. we. uh--
we talk
here and there.
You know. Insta. DMs.
phone calls
every once in a while.
- Great.
Great. When was the last time
you think you talked to him?
- Why is that important?
- It might not be important
at all. but everything helps.
Did you talk to him lately.
like this week?
Today?
- No.
- You can answer the question.
Ellis.
- No. he can't.
That's enough.
- Look. I don't understand.
- This is over right now.
We're done.
- Where were you today. Ellis?
- Here. home with us.
We're done.
You think I don't know
a suspect interview?
- You know. Dwayne Coleman
was murdered today--
- No. no.
If you'd like to bring my son
in for questioning. feel free.
But he will sit silently
for 48 hours
with a team of lawyers.
many of whom are well-known
for prosecuting and winning
police misconduct cases.
So you take him in. or go.
- Thank you for your time.
Ma'am.
The kid's involved.
He must have cherry-picked
the parties.
got the crew involved.
and split the profits.
Something went wrong
with Emily.
so he covered his tracks.
- Father was there
for the whole interview.
He shut us down quick.
- But Ellis
is clearly involved.
- He doesn't need the cash.
so why is he ripping?
- Maybe 'cause he can.
Extra cash. power.
Why not?
- Well. they've definitely
been in contact.
Coleman's phone shows
a dozen calls between the pair
in the last three months.
- Emily's mom said
her and Ellis broke up
the night before the party.
and Emily didn't tell anyone.
So that could be a motive
for the beating.
- OK. so Ellis sets up
the robberies.
lets the crew tie up his girl.
She gets beat to death.
- Yeah. but why is he
the one calling the police?
- He probably didn't expect
for her to die.
I mean. what else was
he supposed to do?
She was bleeding out.
He had to call the cops
to save his own ass.
- Well. theory means nothing
without evidence.
Alan is going to
protect his son.
We won't get close
without airtight charges.
- Hey. something hit
on the Ventra cards.
I ran Coleman's.
got all the taps
from the night of the parties.
One other card scans
the same gate within seconds
of him each time.
- Somebody else was there.
- Yeah. that's gotta be
our third offender.
Asset Forfeiture is running the
credit card attached right now.
- Good.
Keep building.
We need more.
- Yo.
- Hey.
- Yeah. I think I reached the
limit of what I can do here.
so I'm gonna let y'all work.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- OK.
You good?
- Mm-hmm.
You didn't tell anyone. Kevin?
- No.
Because I don't know exactly
what to tell anybody.
We don't know
what we're doing
or how we're doing it.
Tasha Fox.
- Yo. they got him.
Credit card's linked
to a Chris Watson.
lives in Roseland.
Grant High. 2019.
- All right. Ruz. me and you.
- Hey. I'll text you
the address.
- Copy that.
Chris Watson. police!
- Doesn't look like he's home.
- Car's right there.
Chris Watson. police!
I can't see inside.
- Tags don't come back
to a BMW.
They're for an '09 Honda.
- '09 Honda?
- Uh-huh.
- The hell?
But why do I recognize
this damn car?
Can you run the vehicles
for the Powells?
- You got it.
All right. Alan Powell.
owner of a gray
2024 BMW 7 Series.
It's identical.
- That's his car.
Son of a bitch.
- Watson or the car. Kevin?
- Police! Watson. stop! Watson!
- 5021 Ida.
In pursuit of wanted offender.
westbound on 64th.
- Police! Watson!
- Copy. 5021 Ida.
Backup en route.
- Come here.
- Why you running. huh?
What you running for?
Whose car was that?
What you got on you?
What's this?
What's that?
You don't want to
answer questions?
- Wow.
- That's enough
to come with us.
That's enough.
Here we go.
- Absolutely nothing.
He repeatedly said
he doesn't know
anybody named Ellis Powell.
Lawyered up with the best
law firm in town--
how the hell you think
he knew who to call?
- All right. tell me
we got that BMW on cams.
- We do.
but we can't see inside.
UCs have been sitting
on the Powells.
They confirmed
Ellis hasn't left.
- It was Alan.
covering up his son's kills.
- All right. what about
the cash? Serial numbers?
- We can't trace it anywhere
and there's no prints
on the envelope.
We have absolutely no evidence.
We have zero.
- Ellis's mom doesn't know
that. though.
Toni Powell.
She loves her son too.
Alan probably hasn't shared
a damn thing with her.
It's hard to say if he even
includes her in anything.
- That means we can press her.
- Possibly.
- She'll want to protect
her son too.
- More than her husband.
I bet she'll flip on him
to save her son.
- We need to bring
them both in.
to ensure
they can't communicate.
not even through
their lawyers.
- Do it.
- This bothers you.
- I won't be answering
any of your questions.
nor will my wife.
- Emily Johnson.
- I don't think
you should see these--
- Mrs. Powell.
your son killed her.
You look at that.
Honestly.
I think
he just wanted to scare her.
put her in her place.
and he took it too far.
You notice that crack?
Can't imagine he actually
intended on cracking her skull.
- She died of
a massive brain bleed.
She died in an ambulance
begging for her mother.
- I won't be answering
any questions.
- I didn't ask you one.
I just want to show you
what your son did.
I want to show you
who you're protecting.
- Two bodies.
two counts
of first-degree murder.
We believe Dwayne Coleman
died because
he wasn't OK
with Emily's murder.
Ellis had taken it too far.
Dwayne Coleman wanted out.
so Ellis killed him.
Then he needed help.
- He asked.
and you helped.
$30.000 and a really
good lawyer to tie up
any loose ends.
because you knew better
than to drop another body.
- Obstruction of justice.
aiding and abetting.
providing false alibi.
We have evidence
on your husband.
we have evidence on your son.
But right now.
I can help you protect them.
As much as we can.
- How?
- What is this?
- That's your vehicle.
- Is this--
is this real?
- What do you--
what do you mean?
- Has--
has this been doctored?
Is this--
is this fake evidence?
You're trying--
you're trying to trick me?
- No. that's a real photo.
- This timestamp.
Is this timestamp real?
Answer me!
- Alan. this is real.
It's not doctored.
It's real.
- Oh. damn.
- He didn't know.
- I don't believe you.
- Mrs. Powell. obviously.
the more you cooperate--
The hell is going on?
- We got it wrong.
- He didn't know.
Watch.
- Alan. I'm showing you.
- I want to see
the actual raw footage.
I want to see--
- Alan!
- I want to see actual proof.
- Alan. these photos
aren't doctored.
This is your vehicle.
This is your cash.
- No.
No. that means that--
Oh. God.
He's just like her.
- He thought his son
was innocent.
He didn't do anything.
Alan...
it was your wife.
Toni.
- Toni withdrew the cash.
She took your car.
She paid off Watson.
Which means Ellis told her
exactly what he did.
and she covered it up.
Nobody told you.
- I'm done talking.
I'm--I'm done.
- It's written
all over your face. Alan.
You had no idea.
You're scared of that boy.
You're scared of your wife.
- No.
No. I'm--I'm done.
- How are you done talking?
How can you go to sleep
at night.
knowing what he's capable of?
How can you live with that?
- He's my son.
She's my wife.
- But this is your family--
- No!
I made a choice.
Can you understand that?
I still make that choice.
I am done talking.
- And what is the timeline?
- 12 hours between
both of them.
Alan's not talking at all.
Toni's letting her lawyer
speak for her.
- And where is Ellis now?
- He's at home.
UCs are sitting on him
at the house.
- It's a Hail Mary.
- Yeah. maybe.
but we never found
a murder weapon
on Dwayne Coleman.
It's worth a shot.
- OK. put it in motion.
but we need to be right on him.
We cannot lose him.
- We won't.
- All right.
I'm gonna go get set up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
Burgess called.
said y'all are close.
I gave her my number.
- That's gonna be fun for me.
So are you close?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. we're running a play.
- Can I help?
- Yeah.
Let's roll.
Ocean. you a go?
- Yeah. I'm here.
- We're set.
All quiet.
Light on the third floor
is on--
Ellis's bedroom.
- Copy that.
I see it.
- Mm.
There's Ellis.
OK.
What do you think?
That sound like his mama?
- "Hon. just got released.
"Lawyer with me.
provided new phone.
"You need to get rid
of everything you held.
"Everything.
Now.
"Turn off phone. destroy it.
Police coming."
I mean. from her texts. yeah.
Probably as good as it gets.
- Let's see if he bites.
We just tickled the wire.
He should be moving out
any moment.
Hold tight.
- Copy that.
When I was a kid.
I thought families that
had houses like this
had it all.
- Ellis is exiting
the building by the garage.
so be ready to go mobile.
- Wait. what's he doing?
He's not moving to the vehicle.
- Uh. scratch that.
He's coming around the side
of the building on foot.
- All right.
Standing by to go mobile.
- Kev. you got eyes?
- Right there.
- Yeah. we got him.
We got eyes.
He's leaving the house.
headed--
headed toward the park.
All right.
I'm about to get out.
- I'll come with you.
- Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
You hang back.
Hang back.
Yo. I just lost eyes.
I'm about to get on foot.
Going dark.
- Copy.
Right behind you.
- Drop the weapon!
- Police!
Stay down.
- I got you covered.
- Fox!
Fox. you OK?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
I'm good. I'm good.
Everything is OK.
He didn't get near my belly.
- OK.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- OK.
I'm good. I promise.
OK?
- Mm-hmm.
- It's all good.
- All right. man.
Up you go. up you go.
- I'm good.
- Yeah. he hid
all the evidence in a tree
right over here in the park.
- It was practically
in his own backyard.
- Yeah. not very smart.
- Thinks he's invincible.
Safest place is close to home.
- Uh-huh.
ASA on board?
- Already ruled it plain view.
and no expectation of privacy.
And good to charge Toni
with felony interference
and obstruction.
Watson's flipped. cooperating.
- That's nice work.
- Thanks. boss.
- Thanks. Sarge.
- Congratulations. daddy-o.
- So instead of
getting more sleep.
you bring your pregnant girl
to some old rusty swings?
- Yep.
- OK.
Oof!
- I grew up in that building
right there.
My first good memory
was on these swings.
My pops and my moms
would bring me over here.
I had to be. like. two.
- Hmm.
- And they'd both. uh.
swing me all the way back.
I'd look up.
and I'd hate the height.
I'd be so damn scared.
- Wow.
Kevin Atwater of Chicago PD.
afraid of swings.
- I was two.
What you want me to do?
But. no. coming over here was
my favorite thing.
when things were good.
Good didn't last
that long back then.
But later. I would bring
my little brother
and my little sister over here.
I had to put them
on the swings.
Swings felt like
the good things.
I was just trying to force
what I saw my parents doing.
Fake practicing like
I was a dad. trying to pretend.
I didn't know what
the hell I was doing.
- I'm starting to see
what this outing is about.
- I told myself
if I had my own kids.
I wouldn't force myself
to be right.
I would just do it real.
I don't want to pretend.
You're not wrong. Tasha Fox.
We don't know each other
that well.
So if you ain't trying to skip
a thousand steps ahead...
I understand.
I hate Miami.
- What?
- Yeah.
The humidity. it's awful.
All I do is write
parking tickets.
I'm lonely. and...
I miss you.
But. Kevin.
I am scared out of my mind.
I gotta know that this is real.
You and me. OK?
Not just the baby.
I just--I gotta know that
this is real.
- OK.
- OK?
Let's make a deal. day by day.
You stick around in Chicago.
we get to know
each other better.
and we take our time.
Make it real.
Mm.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-